Hans Peter Jonas Hogh-Noori

Fin-tech professional with 5 years experience in software and project management, I have recently decided to make a career change and pivot into software development. Part of this change is driven by an urge to work in a more creative role where I can engineer helpful solutions for society. I am interested in the fin-tech space as this is where I cut my teeth, especially for companies who aim to make finance more accessible for all.

London (U.K) (020) 3509 6573

jonasgeneralassembly@gmail

.com

Linked-In: H.P Jonas Hogh

GitHub: <u>inoori31</u>

ON-GOING PROJECTS

NFT Squad — Social media and trading platform

A platform with a unique selling point as a forum where one can create, investigate, communicate, and eventually accumulate non-fungible tokens.

WorkBuddies — Virtual web development *teaching assistant*

A free online platform that allows web developers to query and work on projects with available teachers- globally.

GitHub — Please check for other repositories with small projects within

EXPERIENCE

Sconenborn Immobilien Beratungs, Berlin — *Project Manager (Finance)*

October 2019 - Jan 2021

Private family construction firm specializing in premium retirement homes for the German market. My role as finance manager was to work alongside the head of finance in sourcing multiple finance options for ongoing projects, and business development opportunities with our commercial patterns.

Capitalise.com, London — Capital Advisory Manager (Enterprise)

March 2018 - September 2019

Enterprise Saas; new business, onboarding, and partnership roll out across my target audience of U.K top 100 accountancies. My role specialized in guiding business advisory and corporate finance teams in developing new revenue services from their clients. In addition, product recommendations for our development team were a key part of my role.

DueDil, London — Business development manager

August 2017 - April 2018

Enterprise SaaS: Working within a pod of three in market mapping and deal acquisition.

SKILLS

Project management.

C- Level negotiation

CRM Analytics

Git, Github, technical

workflow

Javascript

Ruby

React

Redux

AWARDS

UK Foreign & Commonwealth Office - Diplomacy in the 21st Century (94%) - 2019

Linkedin - SCRUM - 2020

Linkedin - Agile- 2020

Udemy - Python for Data

Analytics - 2020

Udemy - Data Science - 2020

LANGUAGES

Danish - conversational

English - native

German - conversational

Carisbrook Partners, London — Headhunter (technology)

August 2016 - April 2017

Given the opportunity to set up and run the technology placement at Carisbrook. While this was a short-lived experience I got my first taste in 360 sales, field-based negotiations in the London fin-tech space, and commercial relations I carried with me through my career.

EDUCATION

Le Wagon, London — Web development

January 2021 - June 2021

25-week part-time intensive coding Bootcamp learning

Front end: HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Javascript ES6.

React & Redux

Back end: Ruby on Rails, Heroku

<u>Database</u>: SQL, Relational database, Postgres

Git & GitHub

Test-Driven development

3 projects see GitHub Account: jnoori31

Roskilde University, Copenhagen — Masters (MSc)

Chinese Political economy - Distinction

September 2014 - September 2016

Manchester Metropolitan University, Manchester — *Bachelors BA (Hons)*

Politics - 2.1

September 2010 - August 2013

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

Afrika Kontact — Copenhagen, Denmark

Graduate Research Assistant

The effects of the Transatlantic Trade & Investment Partnership on the Schengen area

Project coordination of a student street awareness sit-in